ARIBASKAR-JB

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+91 8925137703

https://github.com/Aribaskar-jb

https://aribaskar.tech/

SKILLS

HTML

Css

Java Script

Bootstrap

React Js

MUI

Next Js

Java(Beginner)

Python(Beginner)

Git

Github

Firebase

TypeScript(Beginner)

Node js(Beginner)

EDUCATION

KG College of Arts and Science

BCA(Bachelors's in Computer Application) 2021-Present

Vidhyasagar International Public School

High School

LINKS

Github://@Aribaskar-jb

<u>LinkedIn://@aribaskar-j-b</u>

Gmail:j.b.aribaskar1515@gmail.com

Leetcode://@Aribaskar_j_b

Hackerrank://@j_b_aribaskar

Medium://@Aribaskar-jb

PROFILE

A Front End Developer with over two years of experience with technology, having used a variety of front-end technologies such as React, JavaScript, and TypeScript. I have gained a vast amount of knowledge regarding web development and various other technologies used for web development.

EXPERIENCE

KGXperience(KGX) | Associate Lead & Open Source Contributor Present | KGISL Campus Coimbatore

- Contributed in 20+ projects (Open Source)
- Associate Lead a team at KGX in Frontend development

Savemon | Web Developer (Intern)

Mar 2023 - May 2023 | Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Manage website development project from initial design
- Used React, React Router And Meterial UI to create and maintain the Code

Nivashini-Care | Consultancy

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023 | Green Fort Colony Coimbatore

- Developed UI using HTML | Css | Java Script
- Integrate Firebase into the project for the contact page.

GDSC-KGCAS | Organizer

Present | KG College of Arts and Science

- Plan and execute an engaging GDSC meetup.
- Explore the latest in technology and foster innovation.

PROJECTS

KGXperience | Student Automation

Present | KGISL Campus Coimbatore

- Worked on Student Management System
- · Implemented Inventory system for Admin

Nunnari(நுண்ணறி) Labs Contributor

June 2023 | Coimbatore

- Developed and implemented the "Meet Your Instructors" section
- Streamlined the registration process by integrating an Airtable form

Microsoft/rushstack-websites| Open Source

Oct 2023 | Coimbatore

Fixed the Header Elements Misaligned on Mobile View and Section Not Visible in Dark Mode